dropshiplifestyle.com 2019-10-23

# Terms & Conditions

**Privacy Policy:**

 **Last Updated May 24, 2018.**

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service along with the choices you have associated with that data.  We use your data to provide and improve the your experience with our Services. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

**Data Controller and Owner**

Drop Ship Lifestyle,  
support@dropshiplifestyle.com

 **Types of Data Collected:**

Among the types of Personal Data that this Service collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, Email, Name, and Location. Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.

The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Service. Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by the Service or by the owners of third party services used by this Service, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the purpose of providing the service required by the User and for remarketing across Facebook, Instagram, Google, YouTube, and Twitter.

Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Service to provide its programs. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Service and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

 **Method Of Processing:**

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.

Access to the Data may be available to Data Processors such as employees involved with the processing or to external parties providing services to the Data Controller, third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

 **Conservation Time**

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.

 **The use of the collected Data:**

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Service to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics and Contacting the User.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

\- Analytics Data  
\- Newsletter Registration

\- Remarketing

Additional information about Data collection and processing

 **Your Data Protection Rights Under GDPR:**

 **​**  

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Drop Ship Lifestyl aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  *  **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.**  Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  *  **The right of rectification.**  You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  *  **The right to object.**  You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  *  **The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  *  **The right to data portability.**  You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  *  **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Drop Ship Lifestyle relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

​  

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

 **Legal Action:**

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Service or the related services.

 **​Fair Use Policy:**

We follow the Fair Use Policy for re-use of our content for commentary and criticism, or parody.  Any user found redistributing our content, reproducing it as their own, or attempting to profit from our method of training may have their account revoked at any time without prior notice.  

 **Additional Information about User’s Personal Data**

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Service may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data.

 **System Logs and Maintenance  
**  
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Service and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Service (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information.

 **The rights of Users:**

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

 **Changes to this policy:**

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Service and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

 **Affiliate Disclosure:**

 **  
**Please note that we promote products & services from companies that we are currently working with including: Shopify, Private Internet Access, Klaviyo, and Grasshopper.  If you sign up for any of these products or services through our link, we will earn a commission for referring you.

 **Refunds:**

​We offer a 30 day action based money back guarantee. 

 **​** To be eligible for a refund you 

 _must_

prove you have completed the following action tasks within 30 days: 1) Select a Niche, 2) Find 20 suppliers, and 3) Build a Website.  Under no circumstances will refunds be issued outside of 30 days and without completion of the action tasks listed above.

 **​**  

 **​**
